<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Caspian Acres</title>
    <link>http://caspianacres.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Caspian Acres</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 15:21:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://caspianacres.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We Are Hiring!</title>
      <link>http://caspianacres.ca/post/hiring-march-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 15:21:46 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caspianacres.ca/post/hiring-march-2018/</guid>
      <description>We are hiring! We are looking for a summer intern to help us take care of our farm and expand our integrated duck and black soldier fly farming operation. This is a new and experimental concept that we are developing on our farm and we believe it is a great way to produce high quality and delicious meat for our local market, right here in Kamloops.
Our farm is growing and it is becoming increasingly risky for the two of us to be the only people knowing how to run the farm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork</title>
      <link>http://caspianacres.ca/products/pork/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 22:05:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caspianacres.ca/products/pork/</guid>
      <description>Our pigs live a natural life outside with space to root, run and mud bath to their hearts content. They are fed food scraps from local restaurants and contributors in and around the kamloops area. From time to time we have a limited amount of pork available.
   Item Price ($/lb)     Pork chop 10.00   Bacon, cured 12.00   Spare ribs 8.00   Breakfast sausage 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Hatch</title>
      <link>http://caspianacres.ca/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 23:31:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caspianacres.ca/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>It has been an awesome year for us for natural hatches. When birds are comfortable and happy, they do a much better job than our incubator ever could. We recently had a duck hatch 20 out of 20 eggs and today we just found this silky hen walking around with five chicks that look day old. It is a great surprise and the nice thing about a natural hatch is that we do not have to worry about setting up a brooder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://caspianacres.ca/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caspianacres.ca/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can email us at info@caspianacres.ca or call us at 1(778)5860917. We would love to hear from you!
We are located in Cherry Creek near Kamloops, BC, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>